[Music]
hello welcome to the junkyard love OMI
dudes in my dudettes welcome to the
junkyard love pot yes where before we
get going I like to leave a
recommendation and today's
recommendation is in the form of a ten
minute and 48 seconds long TED talk on
YouTube it is called what I learned
about freedom after escaping North Korea
it's crazy you should totally check it
out what's a perspective on the life for
show today we've got Andre and Beto
Andre and Rob it's a great episode this
was from February 10th I believe it's a
little bit back in the archives I'm
working through the archives currently
as of course I'm not having a new guests
come face to face here with me at the
studio so I did and maybe doing more
video conferencing and did some some
meditation mindfulness conversation this
morning with a friend that I recorded
that I may upload in the form of a
podcast and I may be doing some more
mindfulness meditation related stuff
audio things and guided meditations in
the coming days and while we're on
quarantine here so be on the lookout for
that anyway here is the episode I hope
you enjoy it
have a good rest of you today take care
of yourself get outside and breathe some
fresh air don't be afraid of the outside
just because we're locked inside just be
afraid of touching people and surfaces
wash your hands
let's go alright so we uh we're gonna
start things off with Andre you were
telling me that I clothing is actually
like some sort of front for some sort of
alien work not alien but it's a front
for our space company space company yes
you don't know anything about aliens not
yet what do you know about aliens you
sure you lyin I don't think I know if
you gotta tell me you know you're
obligated to tell me it'd be cool if
they existed I think it'd be awesome to
not be alone in this massive universe
okay what do you guys generally think
let's start with aliens for sure bet to
pull this thing a little bit closer to
your mouth when you're getting there
okay
what do you think cuz like I I feel like
I was watching Joe Rogan in they like
does I think the CIA has officially like
said like yeah we do have this saucer
and we don't it's like actual government
information I think now it's not like
they're like denying it but I don't know
like what can we even do with that what
do you guys think oh no I totally
believe in them there was this one time
I was out camping and Abernathy seen a
lot of crazy [__] out there isold yeah
let's start with the UFO story the
craziest [__] out there right lay out
the location for them that get hot burn
Athey if you've been an out in the woods
in the area then you know where the
exact imagine people who are listening
to podcast don't know the area so wooded
area you go out towards Long Beach is
about 15 minutes how you take Abernathy
Road as you go you follow that road all
the way til the end and you get onto a
dirt road and there's just a whole bunch
of dirt roads out there that you can
take a lot of people go out there to go
shooting to go camping you know and
throw parties yeah use a party over
that's how it was rescued is if you
think it's like different than people
from like Florida per se but that's what
happens when you're from here so yeah
exactly
yeah one night we were out there it was
me and two other buddies and I remember
just randomly waking up in the middle
and I think I had a piss or something
and I look up at the sky and I was like
whoa what the hell I'm like what is that
and you would just see like this light
do
mean like all kinds of different like
zig zags in the sky like you know how
like a plane would usually just go like
straight you know just keep going this
thing was saying in one spot then it
would go down and it would go up and
then it'd go to the left and then to go
right and then it looked like it was
getting closer to us so I woke up my
friends and I'm like dude check that
light out and they woke up and they're
like what the [__] they saw it - this is
the thing I was like I thought you
couldn't do you poor guy you're just out
there by yourself it's gone I woke
everyone up and I was like dude what the
[__] and
yeah it was the same deal with them so
that was the UFO story and then dude
there was this one time we went out
there this was probably like my senior
year in high school
apparently the the story is there's
gypsies out there and like weird people
and whatnot so we went out there with a
group of like eight me we're just you
know driving around the dirt roads it
was probably like Ted and p.m. and you
make this one stop and we just like go
look around and I remember smelling like
something was dead I flashed my light
and I there's like this shred up carcass
of like a deer and I get like this group
to come check it out I'm like you know
everyone come check this out and then
the girls that we were with or like ah
like we gotta go so we hop into the
truck and as we're pull cuz it was a
dead end scene you had to do like the
whole turn thing so we were turning and
soon as we turned the truck straight we
see this dude with long ass hair just
you can't even look at his eyes he's
just looking straight down and just like
staring at us and we're like what the
hook all the girls start screaming and
dude yeah we were like what the [__] is
so the dude with the tread and then this
whatever it was I don't know if it was a
guy or a girl starts walking into the
woods and the dude and the truck starts
driving closer to him and then the the
man thing stops and just like stares at
us and we slowly start driving off and
we just start
saying crap to to it and then dude
starts chasing us and yeah dude it was
so into a crazy music video like dude it
was the craziest thing I've ever seen
I'm like what the [__] I don't know what
it was I mean probably some sort of
gypsy thing or some witch
there's like D why are you out there
that like I said it was like out to end
yeah dude it's like it's way out there
so it's like why are you out any other
cars out there to know like yeah cuz
it's like he's clearly living out there
at some sort sort somewhere by there
right like he must have been there his
home you forget on his tariff yes that's
it like 2 creepiest actually no there
was another time to a brunette these are
crazy small kind of [__] hit me with it
so again there was another time we were
out there we were partying and whatnot
and we decided oh let's just stay out
here as long as we can we'll just bring
food and you know just live out here so
I think it was like we did it so we were
out there for a full day and then
towards the end of the like a lot the
next day it got dark and it was just
like windy and stuff even we could just
hear like someone walking around us and
just like it felt like we were being
watched you get that feeling may I no
doubt so we immediately all were like
[__] this we're going home and we just
packed our stuff up we didn't see
anything
but we just got so freaked out and yeah
at that point I think I was probably
like only like a freshman or a sophomore
so it was kind of like holy [__] just
get out of here let's just leave that's
creepy dude that feeling is mad real
like I always talk about everybody knows
and it's hard to explain like you
driving on the ferry going 70 and you
like take a glance over at the
[__] and he knows instantly that
you just looked at him and you feel it
like it's some sort of like and you know
if you're the victim of being glanced at
you're like what the [__] like you look
over you know even a little kid in the
back seat of a car is something like
that there's nowhere you know even going
70 miles an hour with like a metal box
iran-us you can get that feeling so
definitely when you're in like a you
know a a wooded area like with your with
your friends like you know okay we're
vulnerable like it kind of reminds you
quickly if like this fun and games were
having
it's like you hear something you're like
oh yeah this is like the real there
could be something out there like it's
like I could feel that I feel that all
the time I mean not in the woods all the
time but at our stores or especially at
shows if you look at somebody then often
they look back at you
like you you know that you knew that you
were looking at each other or something
yeah strange it's just it's a Miss love
connection that solid is all these
semi-truck drivers that I probably been
in love with Andre you got any alien
stories he got in the alien or even
weird one night I was out walking my
dogs up the road at my house where it
kind of overlooks the whole town and
stuff and I was looking up at the sky
cuz I know me always just face off
looking up into the you know into space
and I saw this light I guess where
there's some sort of a it looked like it
was an aircraft or spaceship or
something I guess but it did some weird
turning and stuff where it like shot in
one direction and then change direction
super fast and when another plane can't
just do that that's what I told you do
you know if that can do that right
little and and then it just took off and
disappeared and I thought man that was
pretty crazy I need to get something
like that sure be driving every day if
we have this if we have this kind of
technology already like a you know
that's what we need to use for our space
company or what I'd like to use to get
around because traffic is a pain yeah
like we can solve all this LA traffic we
don't have to build tunnels underneath
LA bro we can just just borrow that
alien space time gravity and just shoot
it have you guys seen how they like I
watched there's a Bob Lazar documentary
on Netflix I'm here too that is bizarre
but I me and my buddy Eric just watched
it recently and I hadn't heard Joe Rogan
and should talk about it but they talk
about like what they think like the
mechanism would be around like a flying
saucer of like how it actually I can
move like that and how it like bends
space and time or whatever and they're
essentially kind of like saying imagine
like space and time being like a soft
mattress and like putting a bowling ball
in a soft mattress - like everything
like falls into it
roll marbles it go towards it so it's
like very I think there was like an
important conceptualization that
probably had drawn that together better
but either way it's some sort of like
intense like space-time but like the
only way that that would work if those
thrusters were actually moving as
quickly as it made it look like it was
moving as if they were like bending
space and time in this way and they
talked about it in some insane way it's
just like yeah one for the technologies
here man oh yes I mean for how big the
universe is we can't even really
comprehend how massive it really is
right it would be pretty ridiculous for
us to be like the only living species
out there that is intelligent or really
any life like our planet is the only one
out of trillions it has life on it it's
incredibly likely if that's true it
really does raise the bar for how
special that we really are and obviously
you look out into space you don't just
see life everywhere so we really are
special with everything that we have but
I think there there has to be something
else out there ly something well there
is other planets with water so you would
think anything with water has some sort
of life on it yeah all the ingredients
for life billions of years I mean
happened here exactly happen other
places yeah somehow we grew out of being
like salamanders or whatever the hell
the process was the ocean is another
weird one isn't that also crazy like
space you know it's it's the frontier
out there I'm like there's so much to
explore but like we haven't explored
it's like only like [__] six percent
of our oceans or something crazy like
that like we know more about the surface
of the Moon and Mars that we do about
the the bottom of the ocean right which
is so pretty it gets so deep I remember
seen a documentary of them emptying the
ocean and then there's this depth that's
deeper it's like 20 times the size of
the Grand King and if they were to empty
but I remember seeing like the video it
showed like a plane next to this cliff
literally it started like small and then
it zoomed out all the way and like you
couldn't see the plane anymore oh yeah
just because how big it was all like
holy crap yeah and for aliens I mean you
may not have to go that far because they
say that there's a few moons in our own
solar system went around
Saturn and went around Jupiter that have
a frozen layer of ice around it in a
liquid layer of water underneath the ice
and so you could have a whole ocean
filled of life on each one of those
moons so what is it like what is the so
cuz when we think water we think like I
don't know is it like saltwater ocean
water like is it is it really water
water or is it just like the the
compounds of water like the elements
that we oxygen so that water is made of
yeah but is it like a bunch of other
crazy ass [__] mixed in with it and it's
kind of like a liquid close to water no
I mean liquid water but even if we
discovered gas that we know like oh we
know how to turn that into like the gas
form of water we can even take planets
like that and like okay what can we
apply to this planet and get to where we
need to go yes another interesting thing
also Blair yeah I know that so like I
was listening this thing it's just like
YouTube video I think but they were
saying that 2020 is definitely the year
of like the moon like a like people
getting up to the moon and like actually
doing work I can you go one minute and
[__] yeah so like more people able to
get to the moon not just like certain to
people who afford like the nice
spaceships or whatever mmm no ton amount
about it but it's interesting to think
of there's like some sort of treaty I
guess like over 100 companies signed it
or country signed it that says like the
earth is or the moon is like kinda like
the sky like you can't own it or
whatever but I think it's gonna get like
weird like we're gonna have to remake
laws because people gonna start mining
it and so things are taking elements
from it the big thing that's changing
with space is before exploration was
always done by governments you know all
the way back from building the sail
ships and moving out and starting
colonies and stuff was all funded by the
government but now with all the
technology that exists and for things
that are you know able to be created
nowadays a lot of companies are starting
to move into this space I mean you have
companies in there they're there to you
know make a profit and do it a lot
faster and get the ball rolling with in
different ways and governments to
normally move with different motivations
you know of course I got to go up there
and make money but if it's a profitable
thing
now they can keep doing it and you know
do a lot of other things that the
government wouldn't be getting to for
who knows how long if not ever right I
feel like it's a crazy weird at that
time in like human civilization like it
we've we've like now I mean I don't
think it's a brand new or anything but
there's always been ways I'm sure but
there's a lot of way it's like seating
space we've now advanced like past to
government like right okay well the
government laws they didn't even take
time to write them down about space so
we're just gonna go do that while you
guys figure out your paperwork in that
old wood room right oh yeah I mean you
see you on musk of everything that he's
done he started a space company in a car
company yeah most to ridiculous
almost impossible things to do and it's
working he's changing the world and he
probably will start the colony on Mars
here one of these days I absolutely
believe it dude and same for mr. Amazon
Jeff Bezos he has his own space company
called Blue Origin and they have plans
of going to the moon and building
rockets that are capable of taking cargo
of you know that far to other places in
the solar system Richard Branson he's a
guy that owns Virgin Mobile virgin
airlines they have a company called
Virgin Galactic and they're gonna be
taking tourists up into space on this
plane that drops like a small spaceship
and then it fires a rocket and takes you
up into like the edge of space and how
much do you think that cost like 30
grand or is probably like a quarter of a
million dollars I get this ooh me funny
is like it's gonna be like more of a you
know over the 20 years or whatever it
happens it'll be more and more touristy
like it'll be like it'll get cheaper too
so people will be able to realistically
afford it yeah I think like in 20 years
it'll probably cost like ten thousand
dollars or so to go to space it's gonna
move a lot faster than what we really
think like 20 years from now there's
gonna be a whole of a lot more
innovations and changes in the last 20
years in the 20 years before right right
things are speeding up faster than what
we really notice or even comprehend yeah
things are speeding up at an exponential
rate for sure I think that a lot of
people are like kind of just hoping that
we're gonna get to a point where like we
birth some AI that starts taking care of
all this all the information that we're
we're getting like we have so much we're
trying to do and so much quickly and
it's happening so fast
that's just data that we can't [__]
handle in 24 hours with that you
brain right there's probably a ton of
people who are like hopefully a I just
awakens and they take care of they
answer all these hard questions that
keep coming up you know okay I mean
that's probably why they're talking
about building a way to connect your
brain into the computers because how
else can you keep up with it so our
brains aren't built to go through that
much information yeah it's so crazy so
it's so temp we were we were talking
about that a little bit tell me about
what do you know about neuro link that's
eelain's
yeah they're basically building ways
that you can connect your your brain to
a computer and then you can control
things like a you know a car or a boat
or a plane or just controlling your
regular computer but just through your
mind and so that's kind of the crazy
thing to think about the future of house
how far smartphones have came but things
are getting smaller and more powerful so
eventually we'll probably not even need
to use our thumbs or our hands no use
computers you'll just think with your
mind because that's the fastest way that
we can move yep
dude I have a weird way to think about
texting or communicating in the future
when everybody is inside your head I
know it's gonna see what's gonna be
crazy is by the time it comes around
it's going to somehow seem normal
like just just as like if you would have
told us you know 20 years ago like
you're gonna be carrying that thing on
the wall with the cord you're gonna turn
me in your pocket you'd be like what any
time out like I'm gonna care nothing you
want pocket everywhere I go right I can
now it's like you know the phone is more
part of us than our favorite hat you
know yeah has we're wearing it every day
can't leave home without it think about
civilizations that are like million
years ahead of us like what kind of
technology do they have different way to
see things to you like whoa in a million
years even that much compared to
billions of years yeah us like like
humans are like the slowest and most
patient technology like we're like
millions of years but we took billions
of years like whoever the [__] made us
when I was going on there you know sure
like no long journey it's gonna do you
guys remember it seems like it took a
long time yeah
yeah man it'd be crazy to get I think
that I I think I saw so for the
neuro-link thing they were gonna like
isn't like a thin needle and it's like
implanted in your brain right it's like
a chip
they don't haven't totally figured out
right it's yeah it's kind of like a
fiber optic connection in your brain
they implant it yeah
but eventually you probably won't even
need something to be implanted in your
brain I'm sure you could just have like
a hat or something or maybe you know as
long as whatever the computer is can
just read your neurons in your brain and
scan which ones are firing that's the
way that they can connect it into into
the computer yeah dude it's so
interesting because you but at that
point you know when we get so much
information about like human emotions
and like like I learned a lot about like
trauma and like different like you know
people acting out of different ways like
there was this one guy who essentially
like he he was normal guy and he ended
up like murdering people or like killing
his family or something but he left a
note essentially like there's something
wrong with me you should biopsy my brain
and they open up his brain and it was a
tumor he had a tumor it was pressing on
him and it was like that was like kind
of leading to the reasons why he like
like went you know kind of insane and
like kill people or whatever it was but
it's interesting you know once we have
all this data this information on
everybody walking around like how where
can we like place blame as a society
like oh you're a bad person when they
say like oh that's that brain is there
that neuron is firing this way so we'll
give you this thing to fix it like I
think that knowing all that information
and like not just the person who's able
to like oh I can send a text with my own
thoughts like that's cool but also like
where's the information about your
everyday thoughts getting uploaded to
and who's holding that data on who owns
that data and what does it tell
whoever's holding it about humans what
can they do with it you know right it's
that's the problem with humanity is
there's there's a lot of good that you
can do but a lot of people are always
gonna use it for the wrong things I'm
sure - all right what do you guys think
you are - a wonderful fine gentleman and
you're definitely both leaders if you
had [__] bucco bucks you got the
money you got the scrilla like eelain's
a contact on your phone you can like bro
I need this money for this thing like
what would you
invent mic like this this is saying this
is a magical scenario where you also
have like much scientist so you can be
like yeah this idea you make it and
they'll make it what do you think that
you would invent like with unlimited
like what problem could you solve would
it be for profit or just a way to give
back or is it just an idea that we've
had there are all three there's there's
no rules let's say once you bring come
up with himming with it one thing I've
always loved the idea would is to make
machines that can go out and 3d print
buildings or you know houses and things
for people around the world as a way
that you could print you know water
filtration facility out in the
developing area where people need water
in order to produce power you know nice
places to live and things like that
would be really cool to build on the
other end of things
I think asteroid mining would be the
most exciting part of my future of
technology to build yeah because there's
infinite resources out there in every
direction that you can look and there's
also infinite amounts of money that you
could make off of that so do we know
what's out there like the resources that
are like in so say like Saturn's [__]
asteroid belt or whatever like do we
know yeah do we know like is it like are
they new elements to us out there do
know that yeah or is it the same stuff
that makes everything on this planet
this isn't that how the planet was
created to begin with possibly all that
is hitting it I'm not qualified to tell
you that that's a big question but we
know that all the elements you know that
are here and all the materials and stuff
exists in infinite quantities out there
in space and some asteroids are full of
mostly frozen water and ice which we can
use for oxygen water growing plants and
things for Space Station's or
exploration
I'm also rocket fuel yes you take
hydrogen and oxygen which are GU highly
flammable explosive gases and you split
them apart now you have rocket fuel
bruin being able to like make it quickly
like being it like as in like the
asteroid belt is like a fuel up station
for a rocket sort of thing like if they
had a way that it's just like we just
sprouted up a gas station for rockets
yeah obviously like a spit
well well if you're building like as a
transport infrastructure up there you
would need to have fueling stations and
everything so this is what opens up the
all of these possibilities for the
future of being multiplanetary or
pushing further out off of our own
planet as you need all the resources
because you can't just bring all of it
off of earth because that's why you need
all these huge rockets and there's a
huge amount of money that you have to
spend because it cost twenty thousand
dollars just to send a liter of water
into deep space
big bottle that's a lot of money you
know you need a lot of water up there
and there's infinite supplies you know
some asteroids have you know small lakes
or even a small oceans worth of water
frozen into it and then others have all
the precious metals and platinum and
different things which we use for
smartphones and computers and electric
vehicles and everything like that
there's metals and pretty much anything
that you need to build everything is all
up there a limit it's not it's not like
you're gonna be bringing all of this
stuff back to the planet but some of it
if you figured out a cheap way to send
it back down would be would be helpful
but there's just infinite amounts of
things that you can build and create and
know do with it all up there and if
we're building the Space Station's
you're not gonna be shipping off
millions of tons of metal into space you
got to have the resources up there the
manufacturer up you know in space with
where that's true something we don't
think about is like aw let's build a
space station up there and you know it's
like alright well put a put six two by
fours in that rocket will get the rocket
going like it says it takes six days for
the countdown because it's such a
process and all the legal like jump
through z' but yeah get those six pieces
of lumber up there an International
Space Station that things like as big as
like a I think a two-story house about
the same square footage of or something
like that and that costs hundreds of
billions of dollars to make do didn't
you see it like in videos and stuff you
see them in there and it's like it is
longer bang yeah and it's not tiny but
you can see it I mean it's it's in the
sky amazing and ever late you can see it
you know go [__] yeah I don't think that
I've ever known to look or known that I
could know that I could see it do you
know like is there a specific place
where it's like you could probably see
it very well like in the United States
like where was it um
probably and it might depend on like
obviously the clouds and maybe time of
year there's a website that you can go
to and it'll show you like what time its
gonna be passing over your area cool a
spoiler graybles be like oh I want to
see that Space Station that's out there
in space and you go Google were you at
all right bro I love both those ideas
mining the asteroid belts and stuff and
3d printing like waterto and planting
trees you know we need to build no yeah
that can plant billions of trees a year
I think that would be a great idea too
yeah excellent I love that noise use
that okay all right that's what you got
I've had this idea for a long times it's
nothing crazy it's just like you know
how air conditioners you got that fat
thing sticking out of your window so I
came up with this idea called the cool
air and it's just yeah it's called the
cool air I actually have like prototypes
and drawings like damn right already
ready yeah you know and ostomies is
actually talking to Jim I forgot that he
worked for an air conditioning company
and I showed him the drawings and he's
like yeah there's a really good idea
he's like we could definitely make this
happen really dope so the whole idea
behind it is you know instead of having
a fat chunk of metal sticking out of
your window I realized this when I was
younger I used to love just leaving the
doors open on a hot summer day is I used
to just like looking out there and you
know having that air come in but it
sucked because it was warm air I'm like
what if cool air came in in through the
window instead of warm air that way you
know it cools your house but you also
get to keep the window open and the
whole concept line is have it be a
screen instead of like this big metal
thing sticking out of your window that
way you get rid of you know the metal
thing and just have it be a screen
rather than that so yeah that's kind of
been my idea for a while but you know
yeah take some money to get that going
well hey in this scenario you got
whatever money you want so you just made
your [__] magic door exactly see I
think that actually makes sense because
instead of trying to like okay like make
sure no like hot air sneaks through
these windows over here
like if you just turn in whenever it's
coming in just are you similar to cold
yeah yeah bro that makes sense
you know you know I don't know like you
might have to make some sort of like
screening don't wear like it could do
that or I don't know exactly the
technology you need and this is you
don't come up with the technology to
create it but it's possible the great
thing about every new invention is that
it's a new invention exactly yeah new
inventions that's like a weird thing
like like every new invention there had
there is probably one guy who just looks
like such a fool at the beginning he
just looks like such a you know it's
such a dummy to everybody around him
he's no no this thing like I swear this
is gonna work you know like and then
whoever he had to present it with
whatever amount of money this any
inventor really has or the very
beginning of an idea that's not super
conceptualized they're just like showing
their girlfriend or wife like these
terrible drawings like you know this
makes sense right all these things
that's where every idea starts out is it
has to be different because if it's true
wasn't different once you've already
have known about it
you got to ask yourself what problem am
i solving with what I'm creating right
you know that's a big question - so
Steve Jobs even said the people who
changed the world or often the ones who
are crazy enough to believe that they
can write so you are kind of a strange
person or weird I guess if that's what
you want to say you truly believe that
you have something that's different that
you can create that can make a huge
impact in the world and a lot of people
may not see it at first and that's
that's normal because if they would have
thought about it when they've they've
been doing it first right we're at
exactly
nobody adjusts and new things that
easily all the time and you gotta like
you know if there's one person who knows
like in the you know that feeling we're
talking about like whenever it is like
you know that feeling like you it's
gonna be you like if you're the one with
the idea you're like [__] I think I can
like make this a thing like yeah you see
it already and it's too tight I don't
know man it's gotta be like some gift
from somewhere right it's some like hey
like you got this is your job like this
is something you're supposed to do and
you only you can answer the call you
know
not really the muse doesn't whisper to
to people who aren't willing to listen I
guess right incredible all right boys
let's uh let's let's shift a little bit
down to earth okay you you guys are we
don't have to go into too much like all
of your all of your backgrounds though
we can definitely dip in a little bit
better on the podcast Andre I haven't
had you on but you guys i clothing
alright oh lord die until i die how did
how did you two like link up because I
knew I knew Beto back back in the day we
had talked about like he was selling his
shirts out of this trunk like when I was
DJing out in the woods on these same
trails yeah with the widow with the
gypsies
you'd actually check it I just showed
onto this picture and this is the one
that we did for prom prom remember prom
yeah that's fun I didn't go to my senior
prom so my senior prom I I took this
this internship like down in California
and I was like it was like a hoss to
have the same not kind of my senior prom
but I was like coming to work instead
and so like making up for us I gotta
throw my own prom three years later and
we're gonna just drink a shitload
alcohol and just be illegal in the woods
that's kind of my we would do just like
mix up
oh gosh just mix up like with the most
sugary [__] you can find with the
most free punchy [__] you can find the
cheapest vodka you can find you need
some five dollars a cup as he pulls up
that a that photo Andre how do you
remember how you and Betty likes first
started linking up yeah I mean we
weren't friends growing up but we just
knew of each other because he's friends
with more of my my older sister's friend
group in all them but we came together
work on kind of like a another type of a
business project sort of an online
marketing type thing and just started
meeting up over that and then you know
obviously the clothing business was a
huge thing for him and so that was part
of our conversations and then the lake
came up in the calots County Fair
so I give a hand with that and then we
just kept meeting up every single day
and just in the garage just scheming on
you know what we're gonna do next and
you know all we did the Pammy she spent
so many hours just chilling in his
garage talking about what talking about
dreams owing ya just setting goals and
writing shut down every day like all
right we got to go target this we got to
go here we got to figure out ways to
keep growing the dream you know
sometimes you sometimes what it takes we
got a lot of us have a lot of great
ideas in our head sometimes you just
need like you know not not so much just
like reassurance reaffirmation but just
like someone to like kind of [__]
with you about it and like let you
finish some of your half thoughts and
like right like oh yeah you should do
that bro and then help you create the
whole idea so that's that's something
that super dope you guys want explain a
little bit more about like your
conversations there just because I think
it's inspiring to like you know a lot of
times I think new friendships can really
form through new businesses through new
ideas I think like through this podcast
for example like I'm teaming back up
with people that I know I know I'm but
like our conversations are different
like they're more like we'll have those
[__] sessions where we're just like
three hours of just like oh I'm gonna do
this and I'm gonna do this and this is
what I'm working on in my emotional side
of life and oh I went through this thing
is like just growth conversations right
and I think that like it's actually like
when when I have those conversations in
the podcast or bring them up it's
actually shocking to hear how many
people don't they're like wow that was
it that was a real conversation and I'm
like wait you don't talk with your
homies like that what do you mean
and so I don't know let's just you don't
have to give too many details but like
these conversations what did you guys
talk about like like just for someone
who is like maybe they have an idea
maybe they have someone who's like you
kind of inspire me like maybe they
should hit him up and be like bro you
want just [__] and talk about ideas
or growth or we just I don't we just
talk about like you know look at the
inventory that we have and figure out
where we can sell it at and then you
know set an ambitious goal for alright
we're gonna sell this amount of much
stuff at at it and here's what we're
gonna do next and you know think about
different ways that we could do things
better
we could improve what we're doing um
talk about just inspiring things or
random things you know about space or
the future things that make us excited
and everything and it's just helpful to
have other people around you that they
don't try to limit you know what you
think that you can do you know they can
help you put a new horizon further ahead
of where you think is possible and you
know that you're sitting there talking
about your ideas and they have their own
ideas and you're like hell yeah but
let's go do this yeah you know cuz
there's so much negativity out there and
there's so many people out there that
they just want to tell you why your idea
won't work or why you might have to be
special or smart or whatever it is which
I mean I don't think that we're that
special it's not like I'm the most
intelligent person out there and in
anything and you don't have to have a
college degree to go chase your dreams
you know just depends on what you're
doing and what you need to get there and
yeah we and then we just hit the fairs
and what do we do for the holidays maybe
let's get a storefront somewhere yeah
and then we thought all right we'll wear
and we thought you know obviously the
mall up here is pretty dead doesn't even
get any busier during the holidays
because there's nothing really to go see
that's Vancouver's a bigger area and you
know maybe we could check that out so we
thought alright well how do you get a
store inside the mall and we got ahold
of them and said hey we'd like to come
see about getting a spot there in the
mall like a kiosk or a store and it
turned out to actually be cheaper to get
a storefront than it was a kiosk so we
thought well let's go for it
who's exegete I did not yeah it was like
$1,000 cheap she's like just so you know
we have a vacant space as a thousand
dollars cheaper than a kiosk and we're
like well let's go look at it I remember
we went checked it out and I saw I saw
it already you know I realized what the
store was gonna look like and I was like
yeah like this is it but then I was
hesitant we were hesitant about it just
because we were like dude like you don't
have that much clothes how are we gonna
do this you know we were super hesitant
about I remember we went and grabbed
some Chipotle after and were like dude
wish
we do like uh well scare money doesn't
make no money and hold the trigger on it
and you know I can today making it work
because that's the thing you gotta hop
onto the opportunity when it's there
because if you don't you're gonna let it
pass by and then you're gonna be looking
back like ding maybe I should have done
that right yeah and said we're more of
people that are just gonna take action
and figure it out on the way yet might
get tough and it might be not be the
best decision but you just got to do it
you know like if you're not gonna do
you're gonna look back and just regret
it like I'd rather have the pain of like
doing it then have the pain of thinking
about it yeah pull the trigger man once
you got the story all right like we got
the story now we'll figure out how to
fill the walls to bear in there really I
mean it yeah that's I think like the
boutique stores kind of help out to like
there is like a simplistic you could bag
huh that's it that's a one-of-a-kind
it's like it's not just my last large
it's just one of a cat you guys got
[__] [__] now now too and well it
was cool getting into there because I
remember we that was the same year we
did the Clark County Fair and that was
our first time doing that event yeah and
then we met a lot of people that went to
that event they're like whoa weren't you
guys just had Clark County Fair you guys
have a store now yeah we got a store so
that was a cool feeling too and that's
the thing like ended up working out on
our half because after at the beginning
of the year in January dude our shelves
were completely empty we sold everything
people would come in and be like where
is everything we're like we sold it so
like wow I guess that's a good problem
to have right it is a good problem to
have but it's also like we need more
stuff on the shelves because you're
coming in you and you can't buy anything
you know right so I've got to keep the
flow bro that's the thing about starting
you know start in humble beginnings and
just really doing yourself like not
having like you know million-dollar
investors where it's like no matter if
you're not even so and we're still got
back stock coming bro we still got back
style coming
you know it's you exist ads do this or
you do yeah I think it's good it keeps
your hustle though I mean like you like
you see a I'm sure you guys see like
we're getting low on hoodies and it
starts like [__] we gotta work harder
you know like we got it let's get that
let's get that [__] filled up you know
so it's good it's good that it comes
full-circle fairs and fairs and doing
more than just the store stuff I feel
like you guys have probably experienced
some pretty cool stuff right like have
you I mean whether it's like different
kind of customers what what what is like
the fair crowd attract how is that
different
you don't meet a lot of different people
in a short period of time in a cool yeah
is it fun though like you met with nice
people don't always love it it's a good
especially during the summertime you
know the weather's nice and we're gonna
hit the road and travel around to
different cities and set up for a few
days or like Yakima is like a ten day
event so we're on the other side of the
state for a while yeah and you know I
always love talking to people and stuff
like that so we have a blast out there
and everything yeah it's just so cool
getting the reactions of people when
they hear what it's all about like you
know that's what's the most priceless
thing for me at least you know like just
the expression on their faces when they
like you know they see how passionate we
are about what we're saying and they
just look at you in the eyes like wow
like good job like this is freaking cool
yeah dude you know that's that's the
only never yeah no like that's why I
love being in the stores that's why I
love going to these shows because to be
able to make that connection with my
people you know this is our community
you know even today like read some so it
was pretty cool this lady can't you met
her at the show and she literally
message us on Instagram and I was just
like wow like check this out Andre like
this is [__] badass like this lady
really appreciates it appreciates us so
she's like I met you at the sportsman
show today and I have to say what you do
what you stand for and the message you
put out I will support that [__] all
damn day props to you and all your hard
work you have you sold to be a customer
for life I wish I would have bought more
four of your merchandise today keep up
the hard and
amazing work you do fellas just a thing
of being stuff like that it's like dang
D like we're really making an impact
I'll write the extra goes but dude you
don't you guys don't just like print a
thing on a shirt and then like I
hopefully that one sells like it's like
you get to interact with people when you
tell them about here's what that that
design here's what it's about here's
what it means so when you're wearing it
here's what you can think about what
exactly you know and that's the whole
purpose of the design is that hopefully
you wake up and you don't wake up on the
right side of the bed and you look into
your closet and you see one of our
designs and you're like I remember that
conversation I had with those dudes like
I'm wearing this today to make myself
feel better you know I hope that's why
people were our stuff too you know it's
why I'm wearing it oh yeah I definitely
like wearing this I mean it's orange so
that definitely helps but I got my
evergreen beanie on or in it you I
definitely wear it out in the woods but
I feel like it's like a good I'll take
like 10 minute like me talking about
like meditation or some sort of
emotional enlightenment something and I
just got like my my eye
third eye here that's what it's all
about that should open I love it bro
yeah I really like how it's it's the
whole experience you know when people
come in and they get to talk to you guys
and they I always repeat that like they
get the the whole experience of what
it's really about and in lifelong
customers is definitely a thing like you
know just in our community like you can
go down like you know going down South
Portland Vancouver up here obviously a
ton like you see people who are wearing
eye clothing stuff and they're in the
they're probably gonna get another
another hat next year they're gonna get
another hoodie next and if it's the same
design they enjoy it they like repin it
and another thing that I like about the
community that we're building it's like
people will see someone rockin I and go
up to him be like oh you're rockin I
clothing like [__] yeah like those guys
are so cool yeah and it'll spark a
conversation like I had my friend Madi
messaged me the other day her daughter
was wearing the forever green treaty at
one of the jumping houses and she
literally message me she's like yeah my
daughter was wearing a your t-shirt and
some lady came up to us and was like
I love those guys you know and then they
just started talking about us and
whatnot like the fact that people are
out there literally talking about us
well while they're wearing our stuff is
like pretty cool you know it's like it's
a humbling feeling to know that people
will see our designs and just go up to
someone random and just spark a
conversation with them right now yeah it
opens up like a whole like it's kind of
like a like so say I'm in Sam in Chicago
right like I know I don't know anybody
but I like the Seahawks I'm from
Washington you know I've got coming
Seahawks and I had on you know Seahawks
and and I see somebody else in Chicago
and they got their Seahawks Jersey on
like instantly I feel out of place and
then I see them and I'm like oh hey I
know Rosie dude and I creates that and
it kind of brings out this side of
people like you know if you see a 12th
man shirt you're like what's up brother
[__] yeah but like I brings out this
like Oh bro like you really get you life
don't you like that's you know it's like
this like like you you respect the world
around you don't you come on spreading
positivity out there it's the best thing
- yeah you know we're just putting a
positive message out there and something
that people can look at and it can maybe
help change their perspective or
brighten up their day in any way and
that's even more motivating for us we
want to just work even harder and keep
putting more out okay man it's a cool
community and you know we love all the
people that support us and just keep
working hard to meet more people and
keep putting it out there
excellent yeah I'm with it what else you
got got a fair ground wise fair wise
coming up you guys doing more than that
this this coming year yeah not about
like what 15 more shows something like
that yeah our next one will be the
Vancouver night market that's a little
we do we'll do that one every month that
we can it's a more of a smaller one but
yeah our next show we might be doing
lucky but according like all the USC
stuff that's going on we don't even have
that's actually going on two million
dollars I'm sure it's like more than
just like the like pace and stuff that
we see on the news or on the on reddit
or whatever I'm sure there is way more
details but
yeah I read about that [__] like us like
Paradiso might not be around anymore
well what happened was the one company
was given a bunch of money by the other
company that they partnered with and
then a lot of vendors didn't get paid or
things didn't get paid an artist and the
money was disappeared or something like
that so now they're getting sued by the
other company that gave him that money
and they're gonna try and take over
those events and still put them on I
think I'd be found that insomniac is is
great insomniac is Pasquale Rotella who
does EDC yeah dude I've been to up into
a few EDC's in Vegas like the big EDC it
still haven't gone Oh bro you would love
it it's so crazy it's what like I think
I would die now like I think I'm just
like I'm - I don't know like old man
don't want to touch people but it's so
[__] fun it's so sick I want I want
Shaylee and Megan to go definitely for
sure
we might get a bit down there here one
of these years do you that'd be so fun
it's it's an experience it's a you know
obviously all of Vegas has taken over
like just by it's like everything is
transformed it's a kind of having like a
a theme in Vegas for a whole it's kind
of what it is like so like you wake up
like regardless of going to the Motor
Speedway where it's it's only 12 miles
but it takes you like an I don't have to
get there because the traffic is so
crazy but outside of that like you wake
up and there's like pool party pool
party pool party like cascades plan in
here and Afrojack swears like there's
just so much to do too much to do
absolutely too much to do but it's it's
very cool to be like there and you feel
very you know like when you go to shows
like especially like Electronic Show
like you've kind of feels like a lot of
people kind of get permission to be
there like full weird selfs in a way you
know I got I feel fine dancing around
when there's other people dancing around
for boots next to me you know like that
but that's what you would love Vegas
because it's it's all available who are
like-minded everybody it's like super
happy and pumped to have a good time
yeah it's definitely our community
oh yeah they know what it's like to be
woke we're positive P they know what
it's like to be what's the best thing I
mean pretty much from spring all the way
through
the fall is the the road-tripping season
you know and being affairs almost every
weekend or every other weekend and stuff
and it's a lot of work but it's all
worth it and you know we got to keep
pushing the company out there and a
great way to spend the summer and that's
the thing to like even if like we don't
make the cells that we expect to make a
certain event it's not even just about
making the cells but just meeting those
people that we spoke about before you
know making the impact on their life you
know that they would have never got if
we would have never gone and just the
fact that we're able to get our name out
there to all these people that come to
these events is what in the end actually
makes it worth it absolutely is it to us
it's not about making a dollar but it's
about making a difference yeah we got to
pay our bills but like I'd rather just
be able to get our name out there and
our messages out there as much as we can
right you know while we're on the road
yeah and I think maybe next year when we
start doing our own printing you want to
start doing shows like out of state too
like the Pacific Northwest maybe head
down to California see some there and
head down to Texas and start doing shows
there because they have some of the
biggest fairs out there too right so not
only that last year we met this guy at
the Puyallup
State Fair which is a 23 day long event
and this guy was from California this
dude was like dude he's like I really
like you guys his stuff I guarantee if
you guys were to go to California you
guys would kill it down there and then
he told us a couple shows to go to
because he was obviously you had a show
in Washington you know so and he's from
Cali so yeah next year were excited to
be able to travel more and do a little
bit more in different communities you
know get our messages out there and you
know spark the minds around those
communities be conscious of you know
their actions and thoughts to never stop
growing every day
how do you guys balance like bet so I
know you you love fishing
you like being outdoors and obviously
like you know like when it's
when it's something that you love doing
and it's something that seems to go hand
in hand with just your life like it's
you know of course there's days where it
feels like work of course there's those
days where you like like I just kind of
like did paper work today or whatever
most time it's hand in hand how do you
guys work on balancing like the things
that you enjoy life so better I know
that you like fishing outdoors Andriy I
don't know what what do you like to do
what's what's your enjoyable things how
do you and how do you balance them with
with work um well there's not a whole
lot of time for play just because
there's so much to do especially in the
early a few years or so but you know we
try to take a little bit of time every
once in a while when we're able to and I
like you know just being outside hiking
you know writing motorcycles exploring
new places right very easily entertained
so it doesn't always take a whole lot
yeah but I grew up going to the sand
dunes and writing quads down there and
um you know I like just taking things
apart and more you know building things
or who's reading you know books and
filling up my mind with new things and
ideas and yeah I mean I don't get a
whole lot of time but you know we have a
lot of fun on our trips at least to that
keeps us entertained and yeah full of
you know energy and new things so it's
not it's not like it's like a super
separate like okay I gotta stop working
so I can do this kind of just like a
you're plugging along it's just part of
your life like you're enjoying yes
randomly fits in there and go for a hike
cuz whenever you can just fit it in and
then another thing dude now that we got
into the bigger shop and Justins
committed with us to like it's
definitely helped us get a little bit
more extra time be able to do or
whatever we want to do you know that's
the thing it can always be work like you
literally have to take a break here and
there because if not you're gonna
exhaust yourself and it makes it way
harder if I just don't you know take a
day off at least to just go do your
thing and do you right bro like look at
like so like that lady who messaged you
like if you were just working work and
work and you have been sleeping you have
been like enjoying your life you're
stressed out whatever like she comes in
maybe you're not able to be your full
self yeah that we did you know right
yeah you can just glance it off
they're so busy wouldn't have a go yeah
that's cool whatever yeah yeah cuz
that's busy as we get you still got to
be able to stop and enjoy the moment and
just kind of realize like what you're
grateful for in your life and all the
awesome reasons to be happy and just
keep working hard because you know the
time that you get off for time that you
get to go outside and do that thing that
you love doing is we really get a unplug
and you know just think about what
you're grateful for attitude of
gratitude yeah to degrade do you guys
ever like catch yourself like like you
lock up the store and you just like look
at it and you're like oh hell yeah all
the time yeah thank you like a mission
to yourself right you got a you got to
add that in there man it's happy to be
where we're at you know and to see all
the hard work just coming together and
building you know the each block one you
know block at a time
awesome to see everything because we
don't really see like how we don't
really think that we're that big or see
ourselves coming that far just because
we're stuck in the everyday of all the
little things coming together we're with
it every single day but every once in a
while we do kind of look back and think
like wow we've done a lot come on
there's a lot that's came you know built
up so far good because that's the thing
too you get you know looking from the
outside in like people from that so
you're like oh you guys are super like
successful you guys got two stores you
guys must be making a lot of money you
know yeah I got it's you don't even know
what we have to go through to be able to
keep this is it's so sweet and soak so
quick like just because you have like
something to show for it means you're
like all making the money it's yeah
years of struggle it's years and years
it's not as easy as it looks yeah but
it's but it's full circle it's it's I
was talking with one of my guests
yesterday we're talking about just like
where like if somebody handed you a
million dollars right now like you
probably wouldn't know what to do with
it like sometimes it's like you got it
like you know working the work on the
slow game work on the like building up
the skills like every conversation that
you have is is improving your
conversation skills every shirt that you
print is improving your your ability to
print shirts quickly and in right on
time you know those sort of things like
everything adds up like it's all just
kind of compound
to more and more skills and then the
more skills you have that obviously
opens up more doors
it's a compounding effect you know it's
a little things that we do every single
day that compound and the end result
that we get and not everybody can see
all the work that it takes to create
anything but that's why a lot of people
quit on their dreams or don't even
pursue it just because it is a lot of
stuff or they might get overwhelmed but
you've got to be more focused on the end
result and the long term goals because
if your goals are big enough and further
ahead in the future that's what really
pushes you ahead each day to get up and
do the work and what it takes to get to
the next level and not quit right you
can't quit you never hear about any of
the people who gave up you brother ones
they keep going how do you how do you
bounce so sometimes I sometimes I have
trouble with like like because when
you're thinking about the end goal too
much and not just the step in front of
you because there is a balance sometimes
like somedays anywhere like you don't
even want to take that first step
cuz then that's like [__] now I gotta
hit the whole staircase after that like
that starts the staircase like so you
see like this like a lot of times it's
like I don't want to start this clothing
company because I know that it's gonna
be 20 years of like all this whatever so
sometimes our brains kind of trick us
right it seems like so how do you work
on like taking the big goal like I know
that like this is what our big goal is
like I know we're gonna keep going I
know that every day we're gonna wake up
and keep going towards this goal but how
do you condense it down to just how do I
function today like how do I make sure I
get my [__] done today so where it's not
so well because sometimes it's like I
don't even wanna hit that whole thing
because it seems like so much weight on
my chest and alone one day you know how
do you we feel that a lot yeah yeah
we're all human here yeah and it's a
common a common feeling but I look at it
as it's harder to not do that thing your
life will be more difficult if you don't
take action then you have to deal with
the regret the fact that you never you
never took that step to try and then
it's gonna take a lot of hard work to
survive just doing anything it's gonna
take a lot of hard work to create what
you really want to do so you have to
work hard anyway you might as well just
do it you know just keep going and it's
all about just having the vision and
knowing where you're heading and
realizing that yeah sucks now but wait
twenty years from now like all this hard
work and all the time that we put into
this is gonna pay off right you know and
that's the thing another way that I'm
able to balance it is I just tell myself
oh you think this is hard well guess
what buddy
it's only gonna get harder from here
that's literally how I make myself think
because if you know there's been a lot
of times around my game I'm like what if
we did just give up but in the back of
my mind it's like dude I
we're telling yourself that like it's
only gonna get harder so you think this
is hard just just wait right so it makes
me bounce out of it and be like damn all
right
like we're thinking like that and then
again I just go back to feeding my mind
the right things because when I get in
get stuck in a rut and start thinking
negatively you know you gotta find a way
to get yourself out and I feel like
that's a big problem and why people fail
is because they don't know how to get
out like I've been there so many times
that I've been able to get out and I
know what works for me right and that's
just putting the right things into mind
my mind whether it's you know reading a
book or listening to a podcast or just
listening to someone who's been able to
get me out of that rut right yeah it's
your tie you know not your diet like
just food but your your mental diet
right what do you learn yourself every
day it's so I feel like we talk about
books all the time - you mentioned books
dude what are a couple of books you guys
would suggest right now it's maybe
getting the magic big thinking and yeah
so that's all about just you know like
instead of allowing yourself to just
think about the regular things think
past of what you can actually do and
believe in yourself to be able to go cuz
one of our favorite sayings is I'd
rather aim high and miss a name low and
hick because that's the thing my goal
used to be like oh let's just do 10
stores you know but the more I've
started to feed my mind the more my
vision has grown like now the goal is to
have a thousand shops one day you know
it's like and I would have never
thinking this way if I you know wasn't
eating myself the right things okay so
that's my diet is you know just keep
thinking big because you truly never
know what you can actually do until you
take action and believe in yourself
right I love it
what do you got in the way of books you
got anything that popped in your mind
that's one of the most impactful book
that I read was back in high school
probably my sophomore year or so and it
was thinking Grow Rich by Napoleon Hill
bang and yeah one of the greats if you
haven't heard of it it's definitely a
great place to start and it's not just
the fact that what you believe in or
what you think is just gonna become a
reality like it's just gonna happen one
day
but anything that you want in life I
mean you can achieve if you really put
your mind in that you know in in that
direction and that's all you think about
you basically obsess over what you want
to create and have in your life and then
of course you have to do the steps of
what's necessary to get get work but but
the the power of the mind is far more
incredible than what most of us even
realize or even give it credit for you
know because it's it's our habits and
our thoughts and our actions that create
our whole life that we get you know so
if you're tired of feeling a certain way
or the results that you get in life is
probably the thinking that we have day
to day it's our subconscious mind that's
what influences how you react to
everything that happens to you the
decisions that you make and how you
think and how you feel and every bit of
it so once I read that I kind of
realized like you really got to be
conscious of what you put into your mind
and the beliefs that you have every day
about your own future and yourself
because if you don't feel good about
yourself or you don't feel good about
your future it's not gonna be good
you're gonna be living a mediocre life
or you know you got all these problems
and it's only gonna get worse then
that's exactly the life that you're
going to create for yourself right it's
so it's a like it's shitty feedback
Luther you can get stuck in yeah cuz
it's it's exactly what happens when you
wake up one day and you're your alarm
didn't go off and you're mad and you
trip down the stairs you spill your
coffee on yourself and your may start
saying of course of course this happens
to me this always happens to me it
starts like compounding
yeah exactly what happens your day gets
worse but if you wake up in the morning
and you think wow it's a great day to be
alive you know I'm grateful for all the
opportunities that I have and all the
things that you know around me and this
is what I'm going to create and this is
the person I will become and you believe
that over and over and over again over
time you'll see your life go to a
totally different direction right so
that's the biggest thing that really
changed my life at a young age was just
the power of your own belief in your
mind your thoughts yeah it's just very
powerful man I'm with that what you got
me like on the slide edge there's some
that stuck with me and it says your
philosophy creates your attitude your
actions your results which creates your
life that's why I like to say your
philosophy and how you view life is
everything because that's who you are
you know just the way that you do things
starts with how you think of things you
know and a lot of us don't really think
about that yeah you don't stop and think
like [__] it's all gotta pass through my
mind was a mind you know like what am I
saying than here it's I think a lot of
people don't really like they don't ever
question it so they don't realize like
they don't realize that it's hidden um
you know no I realize that it's going
through them like like so so me for
example like I would have a lot of days
where because your subconscious mind 95%
your habits you just keep doing the same
thing you know so when you're not like
really trying you know I had a lot of
things that I just kept compounding and
kept thinking about and kept just like
refeeding right and you wake up and you
feel like it's like like oh cool that's
like that seems like a cool dream but it
seems unrealistic because you're like
not feeding your brain the right thing
so what I would do a lot of times is I
would wake up and I still do this so
wake up and put on like Tony Robbins or
I put on Jim Rohn or some motivational
whatever yeah bro and I I went through I
mean the last like a year and a half two
years like it's 70% of my days I wake up
and do some sort of something like that
just because I'm like do I get I've had
some long way to come back from you know
like I had some some darkness that I was
dealing with but do now it's like train
my subconscious you know like months and
months of doing that and now it's like I
wake up and I'm like even if I don't
have the motivational video I'm like I
don't know what
[__] mindset I need to be in Brougham
I'm a winner today that's who I am
liking it in in in you know sometimes
the thoughts still come up and some
people know if you guys ever dealt
sometimes it's like you got your dream
and it seems great and then all sudden
Tuesday you wake up and you're like I
don't want to die
like out of nowhere bro and you know
what the [__] everything's going great
what is happening but uh you got to be
able to insert those like like knowing
you have your big goal like you guys say
like you guys know like we're having
this many stores like we're gonna do
this like knowing that to always grab on
to even when it feels in realistic
that's a great grappling hook on days
like that but also just like you guys
said feeding your mind the right things
you know like the books you mentioned
any books any sort of like TED Talks and
is sort of like things that you're
absorbing in the mornings when you wake
up if you ever have any like so I think
when I run around with on that I guess
it's like any like new dreamers like if
you got a if you got an idea listener
and like if you got a clothing company
if you got whatever but you also got
some discouragement you got like this
idea this thing that you want to do like
however old you are like I think I could
really [__] do this thing and like I
want to shoot big but you also have this
thing that says you're dumb you suck you
can't do that you got a you got to
change your mind so you got to change
what your diet is your mental diet you
know start reading some books start
checking out TED Talks I'm checking out
motivational videos you know I feel like
Bethan we always talk about like off you
checked out this and checked out this
will send each other a few months like
books or something that seems like or
the cover of it at least yeah dude I
think it's super important to train a
guy I think a lot of times we like have
a diet of a mental diet of like stuff
that we're in taking and we don't even
realize it like we just check our phones
every day and we just check the news
every day and we just keep so much
negative out there too and so on so if
you're not consciously putting positive
things or the right things in your mind
it's gonna be filled up by something
mm-hmm you know if you're not constantly
feeding your your mind with ambitious
thoughts and goals and things that make
you excited your minds gonna be occupied
by something you know and I figure you
got you know you got to live and die
anyway you got to think anyway you might
as well fill it with the things that you
will really care about or that really
make you excited or that juice you up
and I do that all the time I mean for
years whenever I felt bad or you know
in a different state I would just turned
something on that was positive that
would make me think in a new way or give
me a new thought or somebody that you
know had something good or positive to
say because it really empowers you to
have a lot more of those powerful voices
around you and behind you to tell you to
keep going or you know show other
people's stories of the difficult things
that they've had to go through cuz I've
always looked at it as like you know no
matter how bad you think you may have
had had life there's always somebody
else or a lot of other people that have
had it way worse than than you have
right you know if you think your
problems are bad then there's always
more people that have had things that
are a lot harder to go through than what
you've had to deal with and not putting
down you know the difficult things that
we go through because those are actually
important you know it's just it's the
struggles that we go through every day
and the unexpected issues and problems
in crisis that happen in our life that
make you stronger you know they make you
into who you are but you also have a
decision on how you want to react to it
you know you can look at it as like a
victim standpoint or a bad thing that
happened to you that you have to deal
with or it can be something that is
thrown in your way that you learn from
that makes you stronger and better you
know you can use for your own advantage
because you had to go through it anyway
you know you got to deal with it one way
or another so you might as well make
make it help you get better yeah it's
like now what it's like there it's like
the thing happened and then there's
their reaction to it right like it's
it's not we accompany them like the
thing happened and I'm of course I'm
madam upset or whatever it is you know
I'm not gonna to follow it but we got to
separate here's the thing that happened
and here's what I'm gonna do about it
right so I like to say like I yeah I
went through a lot of stuff going up and
I saw a lot of bad things and I hurt in
many ways but it's like I appreciate all
those times because if I would have
never gone through all of the pain and
seen everything that I've seen like I
wouldn't be the person that I am today
no so like he was saying like just
appreciate the bad times you know bad
times are always gonna be coming so when
they get here you know just try to find
a way to get out of that rut regardless
how hard you know you think life is gone
for you I like that we're all human you
know it's fine to express your
oceans not like we're supposed to be
walking around all day every day and
just some eager state of bliss for your
wife died yesterday
you know it's healthy to cry too oh yeah
good to show how you're feeling about
something or you know remember something
or somebody or you know things like that
our loved ones that we lose and stuff
because you know what happens it's part
of being human yeah but it's also how
how you react to that and what you do
afterwards that dictates the results
that we get in the end of life
absolutely it's it's every little thing
every little thought little action you
know sleeping in not doing that thing
that you think or that you know you need
to do or not chasing those ideas that
you have in your mind you know
everybody's unique and different and
every single person can bring something
out that's you know awesome that they
created it's just you have to just do it
right one of the most powerful things
that I've ever heard was whether you
think you can or you think you can't
you're right because it's true if you
really believe that you can do it you
can do it but if you listen everybody
else for the things that tell you that
you can't you'll never even try or
you'll give up when it gets difficult
because you don't think you can do it
but if you just don't care or even just
acknowledge all the reasons of why you
can't do something or why you're not
supposed to have anything and just you
do it on your own mind in your own self
and you just refuse to quit you will get
it in the end you know because people
are rewarded in public for what they
struggled for and private is another
good way to look at it so you really
can't have anything that you want I mean
there's people that have came from
nothing and created incredible lives and
things for themselves you know there's
always somebody that's had it worse than
you did that rose out of that and did
something better so I don't see any
reason why anybody can't have what they
really want in life it just takes a lot
of work to get it but it takes a lot of
hard work to survive if you don't get it
too so I feel like that work is worth it
too it's like because you realize like
the work you separate it from your life
as if it's like and then I'll start my
life but it's like no no the work like
if you choose to follow your dream you
get to it you get
to work in that is your life you know
right and you get to you get to enjoy
the work you know people think we forget
that we can choose that we can choose
like you kind of choose your pains in a
way it's like you might feel pain in
this way or in the other way of not
completing it man that's the thing
beauty there's a lot of opportunity out
there especially with the internet today
in social media and all the ways they're
connected with different people and
different business models I mean there's
there's more opportunity in this world
now than there ever has been in art the
entire human history right so there's
even less of an excuse to not be
creating the life that you want to get
right and it's gonna be difficult you're
gonna feel all the range of emotions and
you're probably going to want to quit a
lot but that's totally normal
you know everybody that's made it has
always all talked about the same things
growing pains but they just didn't give
up right if you want something bad
enough just you know you shouldn't be
giving up on it anyway if you really
really want it you know you have to be
that stubborn with your goals and your
dreams in your life that this is going
to happen and this is the only route or
I'm going to die we're here right or do
this what life do you get if you're not
chasing that you know it's not very
fulfilling or exciting you know you got
to fight for what you want as bat you
know more than giving up on what you you
know the difficult things that are
thrown in your way right and you know
another thing that we listen to from one
of our mentors was um you have to become
resourceful when in lack of resources
and that's what builds a lot of our
character up you know because we didn't
have money to or anything to start what
we've done like this started with 24
shirts of in Rob's trunk you know in
high school the money that he saved up
from lunch probably gave me like four of
them but it's it's those things it's the
hard times that create the character and
teach you the lessons that you need to
learn that make you more resourceful
because then when you have the resources
you're not just gonna blow it and stupid
things or you know waste it because
you've had to deal with less and come
from that so it really is a powerful
thing to come from nothing and learn all
the ways of how you can create something
out of nothing and then make it into
something right you know I think you'll
be consistently shocked at like how
impressive you can be to like a lot of
times it's like like man six weeks ago I
thought that I wasn't gonna audition at
all and then Here I am like oh we're in
the next step now that things done I'm
stressed about that thing you know right
I think a lot of people you know you'd
be surprised it when you just believe in
yourself and just give yourself like I'm
gonna [__] try it do it you can't get
stuck with thinking that oh I don't know
how to do this so I can't do it at all
things that I don't know how to do that
I end up figuring it out like yeah I
changed the front-end on my truck this
off youtube you know looking up videos
on how to do the brakes and rotors and
calipers and all that stuff and going
through them a bunch of different times
but I figured it out you know building
websites and all these different things
with business and legal stuff and
paperwork and you know how to you know
make clothes and schedule events and all
the logistics that go into every little
thing like I didn't know any of this
going through it but now that I've gone
through the process of like learning it
it's not like you just magically hit a
button you just know it and it's like
okay I got these answers I needed it's
like going through the process of
learning it and like maybe [__] up on
some of it on along the way ya know like
that learning it is is what's important
right I feel like there's been a lot of
like expensive lessons we've had to pay
for no dad but that's just all part of
the deal you know it's like it's not
really a mistake it's a lesson you know
you had to pay all this money to get to
figure out it didn't work that way right
so we didn't pay to go to college you
paid for our lessons yeah and that's how
we learn yeah did you make you make the
mistakes dude and I love the talking
about like learning from YouTube I think
that's so important that's something
that like this will I mean this is like
some around 30 to 35 podcast episodes
now and that's been like a huge
prevalent thing it's like a lot of
people probably just because around our
age and stuff but and they're like yeah
I learned from you to learn from you to
learn from you do yeah I called the
University of YouTube yeah bro I think
that medicine that I learned on you
- by I I am doing the equivalent of
travelling to the top of the mountains
to like meet the shamans in the monks I
feel like with the amount of like
information that I learn every day about
meditation and in Buddhism and and all
these things that I like read about and
listen to on YouTube like in you guys
the same way I like about what's in your
land like something comes up like well
we're gonna have to deal with it let's
learn how to do it right we have these
tools at our fingertips not that it's
like I have the magical answer like you
still got a [__] put in the work like
if your dryer breaks just because you
found the YouTube tutorial how to fix
your dryer doesn't mean it's fixed you
still got I just say that because I one
day I was super prideful back in the day
and I the YouTube thing I spent a whole
day taking apart my dryer because I I I
can do this like the end the day it was
dark and I took apart the whole dryer
situation and I was like all right this
thing's broken for sure but I know now I
know that it was I was like okay I can't
fix this dryer but I gave it a try and I
I mean I think I like angrily like
forgot all of it but I'd like to think
that I don't know a little bit more
about guys I think that some that Andre
and I are both starting to lean towards
too is like we've realized we wear so
many hats like we shouldn't wear all the
hats like him and I should focus on the
things that we're good at so going on
2020 we're slowly gonna start reaching
out to more people who are actual
professionals and certain things you
know hmm that's another thing don't try
to do everything and thinking that you
can do it like yeah YouTube will teach
you a lot but yeah literally if let them
do the plumbing exactly yeah don't don't
don't think you need to [__] take
apart your dryer every day definitely
don't mess with the light wiring because
you know that's the thing is like as as
people up at the top it's like you get
to a point where it's like well we can't
keep we can't continue progressing if we
don't you know pass the torch may not be
the right terminology there but like all
right like we trust you guys to handle
this in the store front and we're gonna
start working on these things you know
it's kinda you know just a good leader
takes care of takes care of even the
management you know so like the
management whatever decisions they're
making is backed up by the leader and
you guys are forever growing past that
and seeing like what's in it what does
it mean to be a leader in our company
you know and that's gonna keep
progressing well that's how you grow too
it's like I remember my mindset at the
beginning of the stages and my mindset
was this is my company and I'm gonna do
everything myself you know as I started
to feed my mind more things it was more
like whoa like can't build an empire
alone like when has that ever happened
you know you need a team you need the
right people on the bus to do the right
things for you and you know it's an
effort for everyone to get together and
put their minds together just like this
you know like I hope there's a lot of
minds that we spark out there just by
having this conversation I hope so I bet
I bet then who was a guy that build the
steel company because Carnegie yeah
Carnegie like I remember like listening
to a podcast I know yeah Dell Carnegie
yeah it was Dell Carnegie Carnegie so I
don't know if it was David I just know
the name Dale Carnegie came together my
head someone anyway like someone's like
how do you build like the number one
steel company in the world these like I
know nothing about steel he's like but I
just knew how to get the right people to
work together right so it's like you
just got to get the right people to work
together and the right people on the bus
to help you grow the vision that you
created yeah the fact that he became the
number one steel company and probably
one of the richest mans ever to live in
America and like make the biggest impact
on America it's like dang okay like you
knew some [__]
yeah it's almost like but it wasn't the
steal [__] yeah yeah right
it about the it ain't about the product
as much as it is about like the the why
the the why really like the why of your
company like if someone walks in and
they say what's the why of your company
like you guys are me like well [__]
alright and you're gonna start talking
they're my [__] okay I get it you know
what I mean like if you can keep that Y
throughout throughout the whole thing I
was thinking about this simon Sinek is
somebody who I ever though yeah you know
we have a couple his books in our shop
oh dude he's fantastic he I love it
excellent yeah I've read a couple is to
you he has a couple lectures but he
talks about knowing your why I'll shoot
I forgot what I was gonna say about it
exactly oh oh oh okay but but so he was
talking about way back in the day he did
a talk he he did a talk for Apple and
they did talk for Microsoft mmm-hmm
or Microsoft first and then Apple and
then he was back in the day when he had
the Zune Zune remember the before the
iPod came out it was like the Microsoft
Zune resume yeah thinking it was like
not it was cool it was good but it
wasn't like it was before I applaud so
obviously iPod like the iPod video blew
it out of the water but right before
that yeah so he talks about how he was
in this he was in this cab drive and
he's a like the guy who's driving is an
apple guy and he's like I couldn't help
it I had it so he goes I just I did some
work for Microsoft and they gave me this
Zune it's a lot better than the iPod
like he remembers saying this cut like
in the end the guy driving just goes I
have no doubt so I'm and so the yet so
Simon said it to the driver and works
for Apple
Simon was essentially saying like hey I
did this talk for Microsoft they gave me
the zoom like it's it's pretty cool it's
better than the iPod and the guy instead
of being like it's not better than that
but he goes of that I have no doubt and
it's a it's a it's it's kind of this
thing like like and then he talked about
how the difference is in their company
it's like when he went and talked that
Microsoft was constantly concerned with
like after that like how do we be better
than Apple like their their goal like UC
said he went to their conference their
meeting or whatever and they're always
talking about like how do we beat Apple
here so we're gonna beat Apple and then
this presentation this
comes up when he has a presentation
we're gonna beat them with this way and
we're gonna be this other company with
this and then he said he went to the
Apple company and they didn't mention
any other companies they just talked
about like here's what we're gonna keep
doing to continue like what we believed
in you know like we said on the first
podcast like I like us like it's not
about being better than anyone it's
about being the better version of
ourselves you only in competition with
yourself exactly could why do you why
would you write there focus your time on
what other people are doing when you can
focus your time on what you could do
better for yourself don't waste any time
thinking about anyone else or what
they're thinking of you either you know
just do you bro yeah yeah your dinner
plate like subbing in other people's
food right Freddie it's getting cold I
think Jay cool had like a rap line about
that like something about like your what
you're too busy watching the people's
places your dinners getting cold you
know and this I don't know I think
that's thing and you guys do it super
well is you just like it like it's not
that you guys have like you know
competition that you were going against
or whatever you're like trying to like
getting certain Lane and can directly
compete against anybody but it's like
you're just focused on your [__] like
we're pushing our vision that's the
thing it's like it was never about like
me trying to be better than anyone it
was me like this is what I want to do
and this is what I'm going to do like
I'm not saying that's what Apple didn't
just saying yeah exactly
I have no doubt in my mind that we'll
make it to where we see ourselves going
one day that's the thing you got to see
it in your mind before you can create it
in reality now if you don't know where
you're going you're gonna keep going in
circles so it's about having the vision
of where you're going and realizing that
the journey is not going to be easy
well adjust to every level you get to
because there's always a new level like
unless you just let it die then then
you're dead whenever you choose that
that ain't an option I mean it's like
like if I quit I it's like you're like
it's not an option it's like whatever
happens when I dude like it's number one
I came up with a company in high school
like I always used to tell myself that
like I till I die that's the thing I
tell I die is not just a Shane it's
actually as meaning mine it I tell
I is all about just committing to your
vision and realizing that you're gonna
do whatever it takes to get you to where
you're at until you're in a coffin right
that's I till I die well I mean if you
commit then when something comes down
the trail when it comes down like crazy
big problem happened it's kind of like a
relationship right like like when you
get married it's like just cuz a big
argument happens does we're gonna get a
divorce
figured out like it's like bro bud you
gotta set that star you know you gotta
be like we're doing this like it's like
shits gonna get crazy hard we know that
we don't know how hard it's gonna get we
don't know what's gonna happen we're
gonna have problems that we are so not
[__] prepared for but we're gonna get
through them because we know it like you
got to set that value point that [__]
that North Star you know you guys
definitely have done that well and it
comes across and everybody who walks
into the store gets to experience that
yeah all right hey let's switch it up
again real quick if zombies break
through that [__] window right there
what's your move okay I'm the fastest
one out of here you think you're fast
one out all right well I'm far this one
that's the goal well I probably don't
have to be the own you know the fastest
you just gotta be the first one to get
out probably break a mirror and then
stab one in the head and they hell
through that one block so I'm from the
rest of I'm coming in and then we all
run we all run yeah then we got like all
right what do we do next and then you
try to put stuff on the doorway so no
one else can get in and I think II think
we lock it in down here
I think getting on a cruise ship is
probably the best or space crap yeah
maybe aliens coming back in do you hear
about the kind of similar to the virus
thing but so with the coronavirus over
in China just a time date where we're at
right now and if you guys heard about
that but there's a there's a cruise ship
who like there's a guy he literally was
just talking about your ego you tell me
it's a cruise ship that's like like
they're like there's significant or
something yeah there's like a couple
thousand people on it it's been stuck
since I think February 3rd under
quarantine all the people are stuck in
their ruins oh I would lose my [__]
mind and there's like 70 people that
have been infected with the virus I
can't imagine that those rooms are very
big I've never been on a cruise ship
myself actually
but they're definitely not that big yeah
they're small yeah they try and pack as
many in well and also I saw a picture
and it's like they could see the shore
like they're like we're right here yeah
and they said that it was kind of a
anxiety filled experience when you see
all the ambulances sitting over there on
the you know on that on the shore and
yeah that would be that's crazy that's a
real-world thing yeah scary yeah I mean
never know what's gonna hurt them
there's been some bad viruses out there
you know the Black Plague that killed
like a third of the world's population
yeah I was a pretty rough deal so god
it's weird to think about that we could
have like massively we just massively
have a bunch of people dying like what
was the I mean I mean I don't know a ton
about it but like even Indians back in
the day didn't it wasn't there like it
wasn't the Black Flag that like took out
a lot of the Indian people that when we
came over here well a lot of Europeans
brought over different you know bugs I
guess that people over here hadn't
experienced before their immune systems
weren't built up to it and you know the
US military gave a bunch of blankets
infected with like smallpox or something
to the Indian people and kind of like a
biological weapon yeah in a way pretty
messed up you think they did on purpose
oh yeah
oh it was yeah there's so much of that
crazy stuff in history
yeah they don't talk about all that
stuff in history class why didn't they
teach that to us in tenth grade I don't
I don't understand that you know we're
obviously the good guys and read do
anything wrong it's not pretty crazy to
think like that's something that like as
you get older it's like wow that's kind
of like I don't know how I feel about
that like like truths you know like like
what you read in your history book in
high school like I guess I get it but
it's not the truth it's best a little
bit differently depending on what
country you're yeah look if you read
like my like my ninth grade history book
this chapter and then you go to like you
know China and read their ninth grade
history book like it's probably gonna
say a very different story about the
right name when just the news media in
different parts of the world is always
different right because it's owned by
certain people over here and certain
agendas are trying to be pushed out and
then different things around the world
you're a different side of the story in
different places
it's kind of a crazy thing to think
about well now our news is even like
like if you watch this news network it's
telling you completely different things
in this news network and even just in
the same city the part like the person
next door to me it could be listening to
completely different news network about
the exact same situation right like and
it's like [__] these people they suck
and then I'm listening to one that's
like these people are awesome and it's
the same situation yeah so weird live in
a very weird world for news yeah but I
think that if there was some zombie
action and I don't know it'd be hard if
it was like I always I always liked
these situations where it's like okay
they're zombies but you got like three
days like I always like where it's like
you got for the sideshow
yeah like so it's like you get some
secret like you know like some text like
it's like hey bro like I don't also saw
him buy this okay you know I work for
the CIA I love you bro like um like
zombies are coming you got three days
like you know like that situation is
easier for me I think that I would just
mostly panic if there were zombies
coming through the window and I would
just like think I'm tougher than I am
and probably just get bit by it or
something about Windows so they're gonna
be no they're gonna be alright boy wait
what about that if you had three days
where you can prepare like I can go like
before anybody else knows though that's
the thing is you got to be able to tell
the right amount of people but not
everybody because you're gonna cause
mass knots Astari got time to prepare
you might as well just take as much
supplies up and get this away from the
population areas as you can that means
more zombies you would run higher
populations like the woods all right
better I would I would for sure you
probably have less zombies out there
than you would in the cities that's true
there's yeah you know more humans at
well you wouldn't know what's going on
like what if the whole city like it's
been two years and they're like oh we're
fine we figure that out the same
sandwich for three months yeah ya know
maybe look for planes flying around or
the government came in yeah you'd find
bring a solar phone charger so you can
charge your phone off the Sun yeah if
your service comes back on you know you
can go back but if you go so far out
though you don't really have service
like if you're doing it right you're
I cannot somewhere where you have
service you got it wind up that's a
thing - it's like you would have to
build like a fort and like all this
crazy [__] probably have to come back
for more supplies - but would it yeah
that's the thing what if you built the
fort tune like it's not as sturdy as you
want it to be in like you don't have the
supplies to make it survivable yeah you
guys you got a poor you second of them
for its you gotta take a part of dry the
forest Dom become then you're really in
trouble yeah once those guys come around
it kind of depends though if it's that
we always have my have it's like the
ward Wars II zombies like the ones that
are it's just [__] crazy
yeah I'm just scooting at [__] you know
right I thought about that before yeah
if they can run then that's really gonna
sell there'd be nothing scarier than a
zombie that can run yeah
just sprinting at you yeah how long does
it take for them to get tired like do
they just keep going until they're like
stuff falls off like the leg just falls
off right and if they don't have any
sort of like well I'm tired and it's
hurting my feet my feet hurt let me know
how they walk around but in Zombie
movies they figured out with no
breathing air but they just walk around
yeah we just watched a warm bodies and
they have like towards you have you guys
seen that one warm bodies no little
Netflix it's not it's not new it's a few
years old but it's a good it's an it's a
nice movie it's like a scary time it's
kind of like an irony it's essentially
like from the it's essentially like this
guy who's like like your typical like
mid-20s guy and he's like yeah so I'm a
zombie now here's how it is it's kind of
like that yeah yeah but but at the end
they start to like at least starts like
become more human and stuff and they
show like the light in their heart
starts to shine oh yeah that'd be [__]
up we're like we got three years deep of
just like we've adapted to this killing
zombies life like we don't see it like
oh that's my mother's body but like I
know she's zombie I can't even feel
anything just killer you know like we
got like to that place of like there's
just Ami's desert yeah you just kill him
but then they start waking up and there
start like alrighty we're feeling better
now let us say you
like wait till about one-inch brains now
yeah are you sure about that
yeah because I always love the movie I
am Legend with Will Smith you know
that's a classic see those don't those
are all whole nother low
I wasn't those on these actually the
main world and I would hide her oh man
yeah the demon they they kill me fast
it's weird to think that they cuz like
you know it's just a movie but like they
get smarter technically but it's kind of
it's smarter in a different direction
that humans getting smarter like it's
not like they're like they're getting
more brain cells and they're like
learning I mean I guess I don't know
this [__] movie but like they're
learning in like a weird different way
than us like they're not progressing
towards being more human they're
progressing more towards being more like
whatever the primitives are vibing virus
they have become uniform it's super
interesting alright boys hey we are
getting up here a little bit in time is
there anything that you want to make
sure that the world knows don't quit
don't quit whatever it is that you want
to do in your life you can do it just
don't quit you know you can have it if
you're just stubborn enough to not ever
give up on what you want keep going
you've gone yeah because there's always
so many things that'll come up that will
you'll doubt yourself or always an
endless supply of obstacles and you know
hard times or whatever the economy might
be you're what people might think or you
know your what your relatives or friends
or whoever's opinions might be of what
you think that you can do but to a
certain point you just have to does not
acknowledge that just do what you really
feel is that you want to do with your
life because you can have it if you just
don't give up absolutely yeah just don't
quit I'll have anything for this one
would be appreciate your struggle
because struggle is what builds you how
do you think diamonds are formed they're
built through pressure you know and eat
to become the diamond and not only that
takes a lot of hard work to get there so
just realize it's going to take a lot of
work and
your journey is gonna be more of an
up-and-down roller coaster than you
think it is right because once you get
to a certain level you think you got it
down then you reach a new level one
it only gets that much harder and you
just think life's almost over or your
journeys over but there's always a
solution and you'll eventually find it
it going and appreciate those times
right guys when you get to the right
level or the level you've been wanting
to reach you're gonna be like damn like
I knew I could do it so he's going keep
going
I love it boys hey it was a [__]
pleasure we're gonna have to do this
more often right yeah combo with the two
of you it was a pleasure thanks for
coming over and thanks for giving the
world a little bit of you brains tonight
for having us thank you for letting us
be here and well my second time here so
yeah there'll be plenty more my friend
we'll be back everyone all right take
care of yourself listeners have a good
rest of your day don't care of
you